plidd.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Plidd Limited

At Plidd Limited, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our customers and this policy applies whether you use your mobile device or visit our website. We want you to know that The Plidd Limited does not sell, rent or trade customer lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes.

### What information we collect about you

We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you contact customer services, voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.

### How we use information

We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account, verify your identity, manage customer service interactions, market research purposes and, if you agree, to email, SMS message or write to you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.

You have the right to opt-out of receiving promotional communications at any time, by:  
1\. changing marketing preferences via your account;  
2\. making use of the simple “unsubscribe” link in emails or the “STOP” number for texts; and/or  
3\. contacting us by email [plidd.com@gmail.com](mailto:plidd.com@gmail.com)

### How long do we keep your data?

We will not retain your data for longer than necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy. Different retention periods apply for different types of data.

### Access to your information

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email [plidd.com@gmail.com](mailto:plidd.com@gmail.com). We may make a small charge for this service.

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

### Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to complete statistical reports on website activity.

For further information visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.

### Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under review and we place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was updated 17 August 2018.

### How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you. Please email [plidd.com@gmail.com](mailto:plidd.com@gmail.com).
